

Address

Ul. Alekso Demnievski, Skopje

Contact

078-631-350 elviraa0203@gmail.com

Date of Birth

02.03.1997

PROFILE

Experienced teacher with a passion for educating today's youth and helping to support them academically.

Experienced customer specialist dedicated to providing quality care for ultimate customer satisfaction. Proven ability to establish and maintain excellent communication and relationships with international clients.

Polyglot, hardworking and ready to join my next team.

SKILLS

Good communication - written and oral skills Excellent conceptual and analytical skills Effective interpersonal skills

PFRSONALITY

Communicative

Punctual

Creative

Organized

SOFTWARE SKILLS

microsoft Word			
Microsoft Outlook			
Microsoft Excel			

LANGUAGES

Microsoft Word

English	
Italian	•••••
Spanish	•••••
German	•••••
Serbian	•••••

ELVIRA RAVMANOVSKA

Customer Support Specialist

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/elvira-ravmanovska-b788011aa/

EDUCATION

09.2015 - 09.2019

University of SS. Cyril and Methodius in Skopje Bachelor's degree in Italian language and literature

02.2019 - 02.2019

Embassy of Italy, North Macedonia Seminar For Italian Language professors

Teaching vocabulary and grammar in the Italian language, as foreign, for children and adolescents.

EXPERIENCE

09.2019 - 07.2020

Preschool "Izvorce Montessori"

Teacher of foreign languages

Responsibilities: Created and implemented lesson plans based on child-led interests and curiosities

Worked with a humble atttitude and a willingness to learn.

09.2019 - 07.2020

School "Intervisa"

Teacher of Italian languages

Develop lesson plans and teach Italian language

Prepare test materials to evaluate students' understanding of course materials

08.2020 - 07.2021

"Smart Marketing"

Customer Service Specialist

Provided superior customer service to clients by addressing all questions and concerns

Exhibited excellent interpersonal communication skills

08.2021 - 12.2021

Vipper.com

Mobility Operations Specialist

Handles daily operations to improve quality of service, managing customer interations

2016 - present

Freelance

Freelance Translator

Translated documents, books and school materials from Italian to Macedonian and from Italian to English.

HOBBY

Reading books, translating, running, traveling, cooking, shopping

